Oh, yeah.
Why are you here after four hundred years?
To see you.
Nice pickup line.
It's obvious that she's just toying with me.
How infuriating.
And yet...
It's time for a new history to begin.
~ Emerging from a Glass Cocoon ~
A band of thieves calling themselves
Saterne has turned up?
Yes.
The Saterne are even nastier than the Ito.
They kill women and children,
as well as burn down cities.
Why don't we have Als take charge here?
As you wish.
That wyvern woman ended up
committing suicide in custody.
We still don't know
who spread that animal blood,
or who tried to take a shot at Oscar.
What are you doing out here?
I was taking a walk for a change of scenery.
You're free to roam the palace grounds.
Just don't get lost.
It's fine if I end up lost,
since I can just teleport back.
That hurts!
What'd I do?
I leave the castle for
a fortress inspection in two days.
Als will be away for other reasons.
If you need anything,
let us know sooner than later.
That's not good.
Should I have moved my schedule back?
Tinasha, why don't you—
Will you be fine going all by yourself?
Isn't that dangerous?
I can handle myself, unlike you.
Be good and stay put.
I'll be fine.
I'm not a little kid, you know.
Ynureid Fortress    Northwestern Farsas, Bordering Druza
Under General Als's command, we've
largely finished subduing the Saterne.
Things are almost going a little too smoothly.
Your Highness!
The surviving Saterne
have just stormed the castle!
They've abducted the Tuldarr princess!
In exchange for the hostage,
they're demanding we hand over Akashia!
That moron...
Saterne    Band of Armed Thieves
We nabbed her because
she was just standing there,
but to think she was a princess!
Jarno    Druza Mage, Successor to Molcado
We couldn't have asked for a better hostage.
Once Akashia is in our hands, kill that woman.
You'll be paid double once you do.
Double?!
Really?!
What a shame.
She's the best-looking broad I've ever seen!
You can forget that deal if you sell her off.
Tsk!
That's a sealing ornament
filled with sleeping drugs.
Don't you dare take it off.
Put on as many as you can if you have them.
What are you doing?
Just a little insurance.
No matter how powerful a mage you may be,
you're susceptible to psychological
spells when unconscious.
I'm here.
Where is she?
Put the sword in its scabbard
and throw it here.
Wake her up first.
I can't tell if she's alive or not.
Undo her wrist shackles.
Wait!
Even if she wakes up, there are at least
twenty sealing ornaments on her.
Once the sword is ours,
I'll open up a teleportation portal.
No need to worry.
Ah, my head hurts.
Snap out of it, you idiot.
Oscar?
What's going on?
I was just...
Um...
I'm sorry.
You'd better be.
Don't let it happen again.
Fork over the sword already!
You kidnapped me to get your hands on Akashia?
That's no good.
Please take this off me.
Like hell we would!
Take this off.
Otherwise, it'll make it harder
to hold back on you.
There's no need to hold back.
They pillage and murder for a living.
I understand.
I can't aim like this...
What are you doing?
Get back here already.
You won't get away!
Rue your misfortune
for getting involved with her.
Hey!
Open the portal!
Are you all right?
It looks like they cast a psychological
spell on me, so I'll undo it.
What are you, a cat?
Don't get dragged away so easily.
But well, I'm to blame here for
allowing them to invade the castle.
Sorry.
Wh-What's gotten into you?
It's not like you to apologize.
Are you asking for a cheek pinch?
No, thank you!
Um, if something similar happens again,
please pick Akashia instead of me.
Don't let it happen again, idiot.
No, that's not my point.
I'm someone who shouldn't
exist in the first place,
so Tuldarr won't be much worse off without me.
Don't you treasure your own country?
I care about it.
Then do a better job
understanding your own value.
At least realize that if you're freed,
you can take Akashia back even if it's stolen.
Oscar...
Rest assured.
I value my kingdom more than you.
You just happened to be
within arm's reach this time.
I didn't think she could shrug off so many
sealing ornaments and use her powers...
Perhaps we need to eliminate
both Akashia and that woman.
Still, with so much power,
she'll make a perfect pawn.
The psychological spell I cast—
What are you up to,
with that creepy smile on your face?
I'll make you a present for my master.
A shoddily composed spell
like this won't work on me.
Who's there?
It's me.
Oscar?!
Put some clothes on before you open the door.
Why must you be like this?
I-I'm sorry.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I broke the hypnosis cast on me
while I was captured.
You're...
What?
Lady Tinasha, I'm back.
Welcome back, Mila.
A-Am I interrupting you?
Don't mind me.
Who's that man?
A present.
Molcado fled to the east of Tuldarr,
or what is now Druza,
where he was survived by his descendants.
Members of the Druza royal court are
the ones controlling wyverns at present.
They're summoning hordes of wyverns,
and using those souls
to create a forbidden curse.
Akashia would hinder their invasion of
Farsas by nullifying the forbidden curse,
which is why they tried to take it
away from you by any means.
That's all I have to report.
A forbidden curse...
I can't believe they'd resort
to using that for an invasion.
It's most likely
a large-scale destruction spell.
But for something a normal human
would be able to handle,
they'd be limited to five shots at best.
Even if Akashia can counteract it,
it's hard to say whether its wielder
could survive the aftermath.
You'd most likely need to erect
a barrier to protect the user.
Can I leave it to you?
I can handle it.
Let us prepare an army.
And you can take the throne as king.
What?
How will I act when faced with Oscar?
What are my feelings for him?
I don't know the answers to that.
However, I know what I must do.
I need to help and protect him.
Legis    Prince of Tuldarr
I'm sorry about my father's
demands the other day.
Your Highness, I'm the reason that
the royal line of succession has changed.
Doesn't that upset you at all?
I was never terribly interested in the throne.
The spirits symbolize Tuldarr royalty,
so it's only natural that
their inheritor become our ruler.
I see...
And it's you of all people.
I have no objections.
If you can't stop worrying
about your succession,
why don't you try taking
an interest in me instead?
Is that Princess Nephelli of Yarda down there?
That's right.
They were at war ten years ago,
but Yarda and Farsas
are on excellent terms now.
Your magical power is unstable.
Huh?
Oh, sorry.
Oscar.
What's wrong?
Is there a problem?
No.
I've scanned the hall,
and didn't find anyone suspicious.
Good.
Go back to Tuldarr.
Go back? Why?
You can work on your analysis back in Tuldarr,
unless there's something you need here.
You can come visit if you need me,
or ask me to make the trip.
I suppose that's true.
But what about when you go to war?
Even with Akashia, a human alone
can't withstand a forbidden curse.
Your country has no say in this.
It's none of your business.
I promise not to interfere.
Please let me stay here.
I can't do that.
What if there's another
incident like the last one?
We've got our hands full as it is.
I'd rather not have Tuldarr as our enemy.
Return to your country at once.
Let me stay by your side.
Stop obsessing over me.
You're a nuisance.
Oh, no!
Please take a deep breath.
Control your magical power.
It's okay. You can do it.
Okay.
I appreciate everything she's done for me,
but I'm sure she has much
to prepare for her coronation.
Please take this opportunity
to have her return to Tuldarr with you.
Thank you for everything.
I sincerely apologize for my earlier behavior.
What you say is absolutely correct.
I cannot thank you enough for all
the generosity you have shown to me.
You sent Lady Tinasha back home?
With those exact words?
The wording doesn't matter.
Of course it does!
That's an awful thing to say to her!
What if she refuses to lift your curse?
She wouldn't do that.
She's got a strong conscience.
The worst she'd do is replace it
with another weird curse.
Your Highness... I mean, Your Majesty.
Despite all your complaints,
I thought you'd grown fond of her.
Not a chance.
She'll eventually be Queen of Tuldarr.
It's out of my hands,
regardless of my personal fondness.
Does that mean...
Let's focus on the war.
I'm sick of having her toy with my heart.
Condemn. Lay waste. Consume!
Druza Mage
My captive souls!
That leaves three shots.
Not a trace remains
of the fortress we used as a decoy.
Its age meant it was due for rebuilding anyway.
Now then...
Keep going and drive them back!
Deal a devastating blow to Farsas here,
and we'll secure political power in Druza!
It's the Farsas army!
Leave him to me!
Don't let them escape! After them!
C'mon, let's run!
Where are the others?!
Over there!
Let's run away.
We'll bide our time and strike again.
When?!
We can't create another forbidden
curse with our master dead!
Do you realize how many years this has taken?!
Hey...
You'll take out His Majesty, too!
Don't do it!
Death to Farsas!
Here it comes!
The third one!
Your Majesty!
Can you heal it?
As a stopgap measure.
Please do.
Ettard.
Take a third of our forces
and pursue the Druza army.
Have the rest of them withdraw.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The next one's coming!
Two left, huh?
I was sure you hated me by now.
I do hate you.
I don't want to see your face,
so don't turn around.
Why'd you come here?
Even if you should forget, or I do...
No matter how many times
history is reset and changes...
I am your protector.
That will never change.
The next one's coming.
By the way, can you see spell compositions?
No, I can't.
Let me lend you my vision, then.
Do you see the black circles?
I do.
What about the lines that connect them?
So I just need to sever those?
Yes, that's all.
Stop it!
Releasing that shapeless
magical power would wreak havoc!
Shut up!
Come forth!
Devour everything!
I don't believe we've met before.
I am the twelfth queen of Tuldarr,
Tinasha As Meyer Ur Aeterna Tuldarr.
Are you the ones who have inherited
the spells and crimes of Molcado the convict?
Th-The Witch Killer Queen?
If there are no objections,
it's time to punish your crimes.
It all ends here.
We have slain King Rodion of Druza,
as well as his vassals.
The two forbidden curse mages were found dead.
We don't know who's responsible.
I see.
Assemble the army
and send half to the encampment.
Send the other half back to the castle.
Certainly.
Tinasha!
I know you're there. Come down.
How did you know?
Instinct.
How annoying.
Did you forget I didn't want to see your face?
That does ring a bell.
You saved my life.
Thank you.
It's nothing to thank me for.
I was just meddling.
I'm thanking you because I want to.
Also, well... let me apologize.
I'm sorry for what I said.
You don't need to say sorry.
I know I'm clingy.
Of course you'd be disgusted.
I don't remember going that far...
Also, I wasn't trying
to force you into marriage!
Do you want to marry me?
Don't ask me that when you don't even mean it!
Hear me out.
I don't think I should be the only one
being saved all the time.
Just like you saved me, I'll save you, too.
So do what you want.
Your room in the palace is the way you left it.
Do you think I'll never hate you,
no matter what you do?
That I'll always come running back?
No, I don't.
You don't want to see my face, right?
It's fine.
I'm prepared for you to toy with my heart.
I'll stay within arm's reach of you.
You've already toyed with me plenty.
I don't know what you're talking about!
~ Unanswered Prayer ~